gittip.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy Policy - Gittip

_Last Updated: May 9, 2014_

This Privacy Policy ("Policy") explains how your personal information is collected, used and disclosed by Gittip, LLC and its subsidiaries and affiliated companies ("Gittip"). This Policy applies to the websites of Gittip, including <https://www.gittip.com/> ("Sites") and Gittip's other products, services or any other features, technologies or functionalities offered by us on our Sites or through any other means (collectively, "Services"). This Policy does not apply to information you provide directly to third party websites or third party applications that use Gittip's Services. We do not control the activities of such third parties and advise you to consult their privacy policies before you share your personal information.

## Personal Information Collected

We collect information about you in various ways when you use our Sites and Services. For example, we collect information you provide to us when you register for a Gittip account, initiate or accept a gift, request customer service or respond to a Gittip survey. Such personal information may include your name, address, email address, credit card information and bank account and routing numbers. Before you use the Services, we may also require you to provide additional information that we can use to verify your identity, such as your date of birth, Social Security number or other information. Finally, we may obtain information about you from other sources, including third party websites or applications that offer the Gittip Services, and combine that with information we collect on our Sites and through our Services.

When you visit our Sites or use our Services, some information is automatically collected. For example, when you visit our Sites, your computer's operating system, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, access times, browser type and language and the website you visited before our Sites are logged automatically. We also collect information about your usage and activity on our Sites and Services.

**Cookies.** We automatically collect information using "cookies." Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a website. Among other things, cookies help us improve our Sites, Services and your experience. We use browser cookies to see which areas and features are popular and to count visits to our Sites. We also use flash cookies for fraud prevention purposes. You can usually choose to set your browser to remove and/or reject cookies. For instructions on removing or rejecting flash cookies, please see Adobe Flash Player and Microsoft Silverlight. If you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Sites or Services. Please note that you may also encounter cookies from third parties when using the Gittip Services on websites that we do not control.

**Web Beacons.** We may also collect information using Web beacons. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used on our Sites, in our Services or in our emails. We use Web beacons to deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness and to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon.

## Use of Personal Information We Collect

We use personal information collected through our Sites and Services for purposes described in this Policy or otherwise disclosed to you. For example, we may use personal information to:

  * operate and improve our Sites and Services;
  * respond to your comments and questions and provide customer service;
  * process transactions and send you related information, including confirmations, receipts, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages;
  * verify your identity, prevent fraud and comply with money transmission laws;
  * resolve disputes, collect fees and troubleshoot problems;

Gittip stores and processes personal information in the United States.

## Sharing of Personal Information

Gittip makes reasonable efforts not to share your personal information with the recipients of your gifts, so that particular gifts are anonymous. We do publicly share aggregated information about your giving and receiving. You may opt out of publicly sharing your aggregate giving and/or receiving.

We also share your personal information with these third party vendors who work on our behalf:

  * [Balanced Payments](https://www.balancedpayments.com/) provides payment processing.
  * [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/) provides website traffic analysis.
  * [Segment.io](http://www.segment.io/) provides an abstraction layer service for website analytics.
  * [Heroku](http://www.heroku.com/) provides website and database hosting.

Gittip supports ["Do Not Track"](http://donottrack.us/) (DNT), which a privacy setting in many browsers. Enabling your browser's DNT settings ensures that Gittip will disable any use of third-party analytics services.

We may also share your information as follows:

  * to comply with laws or to respond to lawful requests and legal process; to protect the rights and property of Gittip, our agents, users and others, including to enforce our terms, policies and guidelines; or in an emergency to protect the personal safety of our users or any other person;
  * in connection with any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company; and
  * with your consent or direction to do so.

## Security of Your Personal Information

Gittip takes measures to help protect your personal information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

## Changes to This Policy

Gittip may change this Policy from time to time. If we make any changes to the Policy, we will change the "Last Updated" date above.

## Questions

If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us at chad@zetaweb.com.
